•SalePrice: 房产销售价格，以美元计价。所要预测的目标变量
•MSSubClass: The building class 建筑等级
•MSZoning: The general zoning classification 区域分类
•LotFrontage: Linear feet of street connected to property 房子同街道之间的距离
•LotArea: Lot size in square feet 建筑面积
•Street: Type of road access 主路的路面类型
•Alley: Type of alley access 小道的路面类型
•LotShape: General shape of property 房屋外形
•LandContour: Flatness of the property 平整度
•Utilities: Type of utilities available 配套公用设施类型
•LotConfig: Lot configuration 配置
•LandSlope: Slope of property 土地坡度
•Neighborhood: Physical locations within Ames city limits 房屋在埃姆斯市的位置
•Condition1: Proximity to main road or railroad 附近交通情况
•Condition2: Proximity to main road or railroad (if a second is present) 附近交通情况（如果同时满足两种情况）
•BldgType: Type of dwelling 住宅类型
•HouseStyle: Style of dwelling 房屋的层数
•OverallQual: Overall material and finish quality 完工质量和材料
•OverallCond: Overall condition rating 整体条件等级
•YearBuilt: Original construction date 建造年份
•YearRemodAdd: Remodel date 翻修年份
•RoofStyle: Type of roof 屋顶类型
•RoofMatl: Roof material 屋顶材料
•Exterior1st: Exterior covering on house 外立面材料
•Exterior2nd: Exterior covering on house (if more than one material) 外立面材料2
•MasVnrType: Masonry veneer type 装饰石材类型
•MasVnrArea: Masonry veneer area in square feet 装饰石材面积
•ExterQual: Exterior material quality 外立面材料质量
•ExterCond: Present condition of the material on the exterior 外立面材料外观情况
•Foundation: Type of foundation 房屋结构类型
•BsmtQual: Height of the basement 评估地下室层高情况
•BsmtCond: General condition of the basement 地下室总体情况
•BsmtExposure: Walkout or garden level basement walls 地下室出口或者花园层的墙面
•BsmtFinType1: Quality of basement finished area 地下室区域质量
•BsmtFinSF1: Type 1 finished square feet Type 1完工面积
•BsmtFinType2: Quality of second finished area (if present) 二次完工面积质量（如果有）
•BsmtFinSF2: Type 2 finished square feet Type 2完工面积
•BsmtUnfSF: Unfinished square feet of basement area 地下室区域未完工面积
•TotalBsmtSF: Total square feet of basement area 地下室总体面积
•Heating: Type of heating 采暖类型
•HeatingQC: Heating quality and condition 采暖质量和条件
•CentralAir: Central air conditioning 中央空调系统
•Electrical: Electrical system 电力系统
•1stFlrSF: First Floor square feet 第一层面积
•2ndFlrSF: Second floor square feet 第二层面积
•LowQualFinSF: Low quality finished square feet (all floors) 低质量完工面积
•GrLivArea: Above grade (ground) living area square feet 地面以上部分起居面积
•BsmtFullBath: Basement full bathrooms 地下室全浴室数量
•BsmtHalfBath: Basement half bathrooms 地下室半浴室数量
•FullBath: Full bathrooms above grade 地面以上全浴室数量
•HalfBath: Half baths above grade 地面以上半浴室数量
•Bedroom: Number of bedrooms above basement level 地面以上卧室数量
•KitchenAbvGr: Number of kitchens 厨房数量
•KitchenQual: Kitchen quality 厨房质量
•TotRmsAbvGrd: Total rooms above grade (does not include bathrooms) 总房间数（不含浴室和地下部分）
•Functional: Home functionality rating 功能性评级
•Fireplaces: Number of fireplaces 壁炉数量
•FireplaceQu: Fireplace quality 壁炉质量
•GarageType: Garage location 车库位置
•GarageYrBlt: Year garage was built 车库建造时间
•GarageFinish: Interior finish of the garage 车库内饰
•GarageCars: Size of garage in car capacity 车壳大小以停车数量表示
•GarageArea: Size of garage in square feet 车库面积
•GarageQual: Garage quality 车库质量
•GarageCond: Garage condition 车库条件
•PavedDrive: Paved driveway 车道铺砌情况
•WoodDeckSF: Wood deck area in square feet 实木地板面积
•OpenPorchSF: Open porch area in square feet 开放式门廊面积
•EnclosedPorch: Enclosed porch area in square feet 封闭式门廊面积
•3SsnPorch: Three season porch area in square feet 时令门廊面积
•ScreenPorch: Screen porch area in square feet 屏风门廊面积
•PoolArea: Pool area in square feet 游泳池面积
•PoolQC: Pool quality 游泳池质量
•Fence: Fence quality 围栏质量
•MiscFeature: Miscellaneous feature not covered in other categories 其它条件中未包含部分的特性
•MiscVal: $Value of miscellaneous feature 杂项部分价值
•MoSold: Month Sold 卖出月份
•YrSold: Year Sold 卖出年份
•SaleType: Type of sale 出售类型
•SaleCondition: Condition of sale 出售条件
